OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 20) 6178/020
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Private agreements: Code nos.6030-6865 (Box 15)
  - 6865, 1995-1997 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    11/1995 - 5/1997; contains agreement booklets
  - Folder List Index Box # 15 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Private agreements: Code nos.5262-5400 (Box 16)
  - 5262, 1973-1994 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    3/1973 - 3/1994; contains agreement booklets
  - 5263, 1967-1988 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    3/1967 - 3/1988; contains agreement booklets
  - 5265, 1970-1991 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    4/1970 - 3/1991; contains agreement booklets
  - 5266, 1970-1991 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - 5275, 1988-1997 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    3/1988 - 4/1997; contains agreement books
  - 5276, 1982-1994 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    3/1982 - 3/1994; contains agreement booklets
  - 5287, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    5/1994; contains agreement booklet
  - 5301, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    5/1998
  - 5400, 1972-1990 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    6/16/1972 - 6/15/1990; contains agreement booklets
  - Folder List Index Box # 16 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Private agreements: Code nos.2510-2612 (Box 17)
  - 2510, 1989-2004 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    6/1/1989 - 8/1/2004; contains agreement booklets
  - 2519, 1974-1999 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    9/1974 - 10/1999; contains agreement booklets
  - 2520, 1983-1993 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    10/1983 - 10/1993; contains agreement booklets
  - 2535, 1983-2000 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    8/1983 - 8/2000; contains agreement booklets
  - 2562, 1995-2002 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    3/1/1995 - 5/1/2002; contains agreement booklets
  - 2582, 1980-1983 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    6/1980 - 6/1983; contains contract booklets
  - 2585, 1986-1993 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    5/1986 - 5/1993; contains agreement booklets
  - 2591, 1986-2002 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    5/1986 - 5/2002; contains agreement booklets
  - 3782, 1993-1999 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    4/1993 - 11/1999; contains agreement booklets
  - 2604, 1990-1998 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    10/1990 - 9/1998; contains agreement booklets
  - 2611, 1989-2001 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    5/1989 - 5/2001; contains agreement booklets
  - 2612, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    5/1992; contains agreement
  - Folder List Index Box # 17 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Private agreements: Code nos.K2920-K3693 (Box 18)
  - 2920, 2001-2004 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    8/4/2001 - 8/7/2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 3203, 2002-2006 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    August 1 2002 - July 31 2006; contains agreement booklet
  - 3208 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Contains agreement booklet stuck to folder
  - 3209, 1999-2004 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    6/20/1999 - 6/20/2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 3217, 1998-2004 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    9/28/1998 - 10/30/2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 3223, 1998-2004 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    10/1/1998 - 10/1/2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 3233, 1999-2005 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    5/1/1999 - 5/1/2005; contains agreement booklet
  - 3278, 2000-2005 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    9/24/2000 - 9/26/2005; contains agreement booklet
  - 3291, 2002-2005 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - 3294, 2000-2006 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    June 23 2000 - June 1 2006; contains agreement booklet
  - 3298, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    uuly 31 2000; contains agreement booklet
  - 3299, 2003-2006 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    November 16 2003 - October 31 2006; contains agreement booklet
  - 3311, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    November 6 2000; contains agreement booklet
  - 3314, 1998-2002 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    July 17 1998 - Jul7 17 2002; contains agreement booklet
  - 3319, 1998-2004 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    May 14 1998 - May 2 2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 3348, 1998-2004 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    April1 2004 - March 16 1998; contains agreement booklet
  - 3366, 2003-2006 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    December 16 2003 - 12/15/2006; contains agreement booklet
  - 3367, 2000-2004 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    June 19 2000 - June 20 2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 3374, 2002-2005 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    October 7 2002 - October 2 200 5; contains agreement booklet
  - 3375, 2002-2005 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    April 29 2002 - May 1 2005; contains agreement booklet
  - 3389, 2003-2006 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    February 8 2003 - February 10 2006; contains agreement booklet
  - 3393, 2002-2006 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    December 19 2002 - May 1 2006; contains agreement booklet
  - 3394, 2000-2004 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    December 23 2000 - December 23 2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 3395, 2001-2004 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    October 1 2001 - September 30 2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 3400, 2002-2006 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    6/15/2002 - 6/16/2006; contains agreement booklet
  - 3401, 1997-2002 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    June 1 1997 - May 31 2002; contains agreement booklet
  - 3635 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    Contains agreement booklet, stuck to folder
  - 3658, 2003-2006 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    June 21 2003 - June 23 2006; contains agreement booklet
  - 3660, 2001-2004 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    April 1 2001 - April 1 2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 3683, 2001-2006 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    December 1 2001 - November 30 2006; contains agreement booklet
  - 3689, 2001-2006 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - 3693, 1988-2005 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    November 5 1988 - November 2 1991; November 2 1991 - November 5 1994; November 5 1994 - October 17 1998; October 17 1998 - October 19 2001; October 19 2001 - April 24 2005
  - Folder List Index Box #18 (Box 18, Folder 33)
- Private agreements: Code nos.1682-7902 (Box 19)
  - 1682, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    5/2002; contains agreement booklets
  - 1687, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    5/1991; contains agreement booklets
  - 1688, 1975-1989 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    5/1975 - 6/1989; contains agreement booklets
  - 1689, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    12/1986; contains agreements
  - 7704, 1992-2002 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    11/1992 - 9/2002; contains agreement booklets
  - 7704, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    11/1995; contains agreements
  - 7709, 1993-2003 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    11/1993 - 11/2003; contains agreement packets
  - 7718, 1967-2000 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    4/1967 - 7/2000
  - 7815, 1998-2001 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    10/1998 - 9/2001
  - 7902, 1971-1996 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    4/1971 - 2/1996; contains agreement booklets
  - Folder List Index Box #19 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Private agreements: Code nos.1-259 (Box 20)
  - 2, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    8/6/2004; contains agreement booklets
  - 9, 1990-1999 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    3/5/1990 - 3/1/1999; contains agreement books
  - 19, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    6/28/2003; contains agreement booklet
  - 21, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    9/30/2003; contains agreement booklets
  - 28, 1993-1996 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    9/1993 - 9/1996; contains agreement booklet
  - 217, 1982-2003 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    8/1982 - 4/2003; contains agreement booklets
  - 240, 1974-1995 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    11/1974 - 11/1995;; contains agreements
  - 253, 1976-2003 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    6/1976 - 6/2003; contains agreement booklets
  - 254, 1963-1997 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    3/1963 - 5/1997; contains agreement booklets
  - 258, 1985-2000 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    4/1985 - 3/2000; contains agreements
  - 259, 1980-1997 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    3/1980 - 3/1997; contains agreement booklets
  - Folder List Index Box # 20 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Private agreements: Code nos.K5248-K5770 (Box 21)
  - 5248, 1985-1994 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    3/1985 - 3/1994; contains agreement booklets
  - 5302, 2002-2005 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    January 1 2002 - January 29 2005;; contains agreement booklet
  - 5419, 2001-2006 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    June 16 2001 - June 15 2006; contains agreement booklet
  - 5420, 2001-2006 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - 5433, 2002-2005 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    January 1 2002 - December 31 2005; contains agreement booklet
  - 5700, 2003-2005 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    6/18/2003 - 12/10/2005; contains agreement
  - 5701, 2003-2005 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    11/8/2003 - 12/10/2005; contains agreement booklets
  - 5701, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    May 12 2002 - November 8 2003; contains agreement booklet
  - 5705, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    October 27 2000; contains agreement booklet
  - 5712, 2002-2005 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    May 12 2002 - May 7 2005; contains agreement booklet
  - 5713, 2003-2006 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    September 28 2003 - March 25 2006; contains agreement booklet
  - 5715, 2001-2005 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    October 28 2001 - October 23 2005; contains agreement booklet
  - 5719, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    August 16 2001; contains agreement booklet
  - 5721, 2002-2005 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    March 17 2002 - March 19 2005; contains agreement booklet
  - 5727, 1998-2003 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    June 28 1998 - June 28 2003; contains agreement booklet
  - 5734, 2003-2005 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    August 17 2003 - August 13 2005; contains agreement booklet
  - 5736, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    August 6 2000; contains agreement booklet
  - 5738, 2000-2003 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    August 6 2000 - August 2 2003; contains agreement booklet
  - 5740, 2000-2003 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    October 27 2000 - August 2 2003; contains agreement booklet
  - 5741, 2000-2003 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - 5744, 2000-2003 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    August 6 2000 - August 3 2003; contains agreement booklet
  - 5752, 2001-2004 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    February 5 2001 - April 1 2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 5763, 2001-2004 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    August 5 2001 - August 7 2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 5770, 2002-2005 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    May 19 2002 - May 28 2005; contains agreement booklet
  - Folder List Index Box # 21 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Private agreements: Code nos.8731-9016 (Box 22)
  - 8731, 2000-2004 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    June 1 2000 - May 31 2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 8734, 2003-2005 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    May 1 2003 - April 30 2005; contains agreement booklet
  - 8736, 1999-2003 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    May 1 1999 - April 30 2003; contains agreement booklet
  - 8737, 2003-2005 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - 8738, 2003-2005 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - 8741, 2001-2004 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - 8746, 1993-1996 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    7/1/1993 - 6/30/1996; contains agreement booklet
  - 8747, 1997-2004 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    June 1 1997 - May 31 2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 8748, 1999-2002 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    7/1/1999 - 6/30/2002; contains agreement booklet
  - 8752, 1999-2005 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    7/1/1999 - 6/30/2005; contains agreement booklet
  - 8753, 1999-2005 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - 8755, 1999-2002 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - 8756, 2002-2005 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - 8762, 2000-2005 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    May 1 2000 - April 30 2005; contains agreement booklet
  - 8763, 2002-2005 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    September 1 2002 - August 31 2005; contains agreement
  - 8766, 2002-2005 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    June 1 2002 - May 31 2005; contains agreement booklet
  - 8771, 1999-2002 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    May 1 1999 - April 30 2002; contains agreement booklet
  - 8776, 1999-2002 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    May 27 1999 - May 8 2002; contains agreement booklet
  - 8778, 2000-2004 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - 8784, 1999-2004 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    8/1/1999 - 7/31/2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 8789, 2001-2004 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    May 1 2001 - April 30 2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 8798, 1999-2004 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    8/1/1999 - 7/31/2004; contains agreement
  - 8800, 2000-2003 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    10/1/2000 - 10/1/2003; contains agreement
  - 8803, 2002-2005 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    Contains agreement
  - 8806, 2002-2005 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    6/1/2002 - 5/31/2005; contains agreement
  - 8811, 2000-2004 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    May 1 2000 - April 30 2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 8813, 2000-2004 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - 8815, 1995-2004 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    May 1 1995 - May 3 2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 8816, 2000-2004 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - 8820, 2002-2005 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    June 5 2002 - May 31 2005
  - 8829, 2002-2005 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    July 1 2002 - June 30 2005
  - 8831, 1999-2004 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    9/1/1999 - 9/1/2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 8833, 1998-2005 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    7/1/1998 - 6/30/2005; contains agreement booklet
  - 8834, 2002-2005 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    7/1/2002 - 6/30/2005
  - 8840, 2000-2004 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    2/1/2000 - 12/31/2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 8869, 1999-2004 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    6/1/1999 - 5/31/2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 8888, 2000-2004 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    1/1/2000 - 12/31/2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 8910, 2001-2004 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    June 4 2001 - April 30 2004
  - 8971, 1999-2004 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    5/1/1999 - 4/30/2004
  - 8924, 2002-2005 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    7/1/2002 - 6/30/2005; contains agreement booklet
  - 8946, 2001-2004 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - 8956, 1999-2003 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    January 1 1999 - December 31 2003
  - 8962, 2001-2005 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    August 1 2001 - July 31 2005
  - 8965, 2002-2005 (Box 22, Folder 44)
    10/1/2002 - 9/30/2005
  - 8977, 2001-2004 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    August 1 2001 - July 31 2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 8981, 2001-2003 (Box 22, Folder 46)
    1/1/2001 - 12/31/2003
  - 8991, 2001-2003 (Box 22, Folder 47)
    6/18/2001 - 5/31/2003
  - 8995, 2002-2005 (Box 22, Folder 48)
    4/1/2002 - 3/31/2005
  - 8996, 2000-2005 (Box 22, Folder 49)
    September 1 2000 - August 31 2005; contains agreement booklets
  - 8997, 1999-2003 (Box 22, Folder 50)
    June 1 1999 - May 31 2003; contains agreement booklet
  - 8999, 1999-2004 (Box 22, Folder 51)
    June 1 1999 - June 30 2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 9001, 2001-2005 (Box 22, Folder 52)
    5/1/2001 - 4/30/2005; contains agreement booklet
  - 9009, 2000-2005 (Box 22, Folder 53)
    June 1 2000 - May 31 2005; contains agreement booklet
  - 9010, 1992-2004 (Box 22, Folder 54)
    1/19992 - 5/2004; contains agreement booklets
  - 9011, 1992-2004 (Box 22, Folder 55)
    1/1992 - 5/2004; contains agreement booklets
  - 9012, 1999-2004 (Box 22, Folder 56)
    5/1999 - 5/2004
  - 9013, 1997-2004 (Box 22, Folder 57)
    9/1997 - 11/2004; contains agreement booklets
  - 9013, 2000-2004 (Box 22, Folder 58)
    November 20 2000 - November 21 2004; contains agreement booklet
  - 9016, 2002-2004 (Box 22, Folder 59)
    5/1/2002 - 5/1/2004; contains agreement booklet
  - Folder List Index Box # 22 (Box 22, Folder 60)
- Private agreements: Code nos.876-1119 (Box 23)
  - 876, 1970-2001 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    5/1970 - 5/2001; contains agreement booklets
  - 889, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    6/1991; contains agreement booklets
  - 890, 1974-1980 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    5/1974 - 9/1980
  - 891, 1977-1986 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    3/1977 - 2/1986; contains agreement booklet
  - 894, 1981-1990 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    10/1981 - 10/1990
  - 1004, 1975-1996 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    5/1975 - 5/1996; contains agreement booklets
  - 1006, 1983-2000 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    5/1983 - 5/2000; contains agreement booklets
  - 1103, 1985-1988 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    10/1985 - 10/1988
  - 1115, 1963-1975 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    8/1963 - 8/1975
  - 1118, 1965-1986 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    6/1965 - 1/1986; contains agreement booklets
  - 1119, 1967-1979 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    5/1967 - 5/1979
- Private agreements: Code nos.507-867 (Box 24)
  - 507, 1962-1995 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    1/1962 - 1/1995; contains agreement booklets
  - 508, 1962-1998 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    1/1962 - 1/1998; contains agreement booklets
  - 609, 1974-2000 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    7/1974 - 6/2000; contains agreement booklets
  - 611, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    1/1998; contains agreement booklets
  - 618, 1973-1982 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    7/1973 - 5/1982; contains agreement booklets
  - 646, 1992-1998 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    11/1992 - 11/1998; contains agreement booklets
  - 801, 1998-2002 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    4/1998 - 4/2002; contains agreement booklets
  - 804, 1972-1985 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    9/1972 - 8/1985; contains agreement booklets
  - 827, 1997-2001 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    5/1997 - 5/2001; contains agreement booklets
  - 867, 1972-1992 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    9/1972 - 8/1992
  - Folder List Index Box # 24 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Public agreements: Code nos.811714-811877 (Box 25)
  - 811714, 2002-2004 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    City of Phoenix; 2002-2004
  - 811715, 2002-2004 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - 811779, 2005-2006 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    City of Cincinnati; 2005-2006
  - 811808, 2002-2005 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    Commissioner of Labor Relations; 2002-2005
  - 811811, 2003-2005 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    White Collar/Food Service
  - 811821, 2001-2004 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    Heads of department, Office or Bureaus
  - 811822, 2002-2004 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    Heads of Department, Office or Bureaus
  - 811823, 2002-2004 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    City of Phoenix
  - 811825, 2003-2004 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    Head department, Offices of Bureaus Represented
  - 811826, 2001-2006 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    Administration Head of Fire Department
  - 811829, 2001-2004 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    Head Department Offices of Bureaus represented
  - 811830, 2003-2006 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    Board of Police Commissioners
  - 811831, 2000-2002 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    Commissioners of Labor Relations H&H
  - 811832, 2002-2004 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - 811833, 2002-2005 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    Commissioners of Labor Relation H&H
  - 811835, 1999-2004 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    Waterbury Board of Education
  - 811836, 2000-2003 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    Commissioners of Labor Relations
  - 811837, 2000-2002 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - 811838, 2000-2003 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    Commissioner of Labor Relations NY
  - 811839, 1995-2000 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    Patrolmen's Benevolent Association
  - 811840, 2000-2005 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - 811841, 1987-1988 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    Consolidated City of Greater Indianapolis
  - 811843, 2002-2005 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    City of Los Angeles Department of Water and Power
  - 811845, 2000-2003 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    Council of DC
  - 811846, 2002-2005 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - 811847, 2002-2004 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - 811850, 2003-2004 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    Baltimore City Police Department
  - 811853, 2001-2005 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    Las Vegas Metropolitan Police Department
  - 811855, 2003-2006 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    Anchorage School District
  - 811857, 2001-2004 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    Moreno Valley Unified School District
  - 811858, 2002-2005 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    Orange Unified School District
  - 811859, 2001-2004 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - 811863, 2001-2003 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - 811865, 2001-2004 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    City of Cleveland
  - 811870, 2002-2005 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    Unified Teachers of Flint, Inc.
  - 811869, 2002-2005 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    City of Antonio
  - 811871, 2002-2005 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    New Bedford School Committee
  - 811872, 2001-2002 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    Board of Education Independent School District #89 Oklahoma
  - 811874, 2003-2005 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    City of Indianapolis
  - 811875, 1990-1995 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    City of Baltimore
  - 811876, 2000-2003 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    City of NY
  - 811877, 2001-2002 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Folder List Index Box # 25 (Box 25, Folder 43)
- Public agreements: Code nos.840023-840113 (Box 26)
  - 840023, 2003-2006 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Orleans Parish School Board
  - 840024, 2002-2004 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    Lowell School Committee
  - 840025, 2000-2003 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Greater Cleveland Regional Transit
  - 840026, 2002-2005 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    Vallejo City Unified School District
  - 840029, 2003-2005 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    NY City Transit Authority
  - 840030, 1999-2002 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - 840031, 1999-2001 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    King County Metro Transit
  - 840032, 2000-2004 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    Jefferson County Public Schools
  - 840036, 1999-2002 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    VIA Metro Transit
  - 840037, 2003-2005 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    Ramsey County
  - 840041, 2001-2002 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    Massachusetts Bay Transport Authority
  - 840042, 2000-2003 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    Boise School District
  - 840043, 2000-2003 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    Warwick School Committee
  - 840044, 2004-2006 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    Toledo Board of Education
  - 840045, 2002-2004 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    County of Middlesex
  - 840046, 2003-2006 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    University of Medicine and Dentistry of NJ
  - 840047, 2003-2006 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    Washoe County School District
  - 840048, 1997-2002 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    The Port Authority of NY and NJ
  - 840050, 2003-2005 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    Springfield School District 186
  - 840051, 2001-2004 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    Cherry Hill Township Board of Education
  - 840052, 2003-2005 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    Ann Arbor Board of Education
  - 840054, 1998-2003 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    NYC Transit Authority
  - 840058, 2003-2006 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    Woodbridge Township Board of Education
  - 840059, 2000-2004 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    Paterson School District
  - 840060, 2002-2003 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - 840061, 1999-2003 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - 840062, 2000-2002 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    City of New York
  - 840063, 2003-2006 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    School Board of Volusia County
  - 840064, 2004-2005 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    Southeast Pennsylvania Transit Authority
  - 840069, 2000-2003 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    Metro Transit
  - 840072, 2002-2004 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    WMATA
  - 840076, 1998-2003 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    Tri Met Tarns Dist. Of Oregon
  - 840085, 1998-2002 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    Bi-State Development Agency
  - 840086, 1998-2001 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    MARTA
  - 840087, 2002-2005 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    DC Government
  - 840089, 2000-2004 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    San Francisco Municipal Transit Agency
  - 840090, 2001-2004 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    Board of Trustees of University of Massachusetts
  - 840103, 2001-2002 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - 840104, 2002-2005 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - 840107, 2000-2002 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    NYC Housing Authority
  - 840108, 1995-2000 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - 840109, 2000-2003 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    NY State Thruway Authority
  - 840110, 2002-2005 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    Miami-Dade County Aviation
  - 840111, 2002-2005 (Box 26, Folder 44)
    University of Maine System
  - 840112, 2002-2006 (Box 26, Folder 45)
    State of Connecticut
  - 840113, 2002-2005 (Box 26, Folder 46)
    Los Angeles Unified School district
  - Folder List Index Box # 26 (Box 26, Folder 47)
- Private agreements: Code nos.2614-2969 (Box 27)
  - 2614, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    10/1993; contains agreement booklets
  - 2619, 1983-1996 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    10/1983 - 11/1996; contains agreement booklets
  - 2664, 1987-2004 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    12/1987 - 1/1/2004; contains agreement booklets
  - 2675, 1992-2006 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    6/12/1992 - 5/31/2006; contains agreement booklets
  - 2902, 1981-1996 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    3/1981 - 4/1996; contains agreement booklets
  - 2903, 1986-1993 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    2/1986 - 2/1993; contains agreement booklets
  - 2904, 1981-1999 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    3/1981 - 3/1999; contains agreement booklets
  - 2908, 1979-2003 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    5/1979 - 5/2003; contains agreement booklets
  - 2919, 2001-2004 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    2/2001 - 2/2004; contains agreement booklets
  - 2962, 1986-1992 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    8/1986 - 8/1992; contains agreement booklets
  - 2969, 1981-1998 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    2/1981 - 2/1998; contains agreement booklets
  - Folder List Index Box # 27 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Private agreements: Code nos.2973-3674 (Box 28)
  - 2973, 1985-1991 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    4/1985 - 4/1991; contains agreement booklets
  - 2991, 1991-1993 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    1/1991 - 10/1993
  - 2989, 1982-1985 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    3/1982 - 3/1985; contains agreement booklets
  - 2981, 1975-1998 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    11/1975 - 11/1998